[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress played the role of Margaret White (Carrie\u2019s mother) in the horror film \u201cCarrie\u201d?", "correct_answer": "Piper Laurie", "incorrect_answers": ["Agnes Moorehead", "Millie Silverqueen", "Betty Buckley"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the poisoned food item that Indiana Jones almost ate in the 1981 blockbuster Raiders of the Lost Ark?", "correct_answer": "Date", "incorrect_answers": ["Apple", "Prune", "Grape"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1995 movie is this quote from: You ever watched a man die? If you watch very closely, you can sometimes see the soul escaping. And if youre very quick, you can catch it.?", "correct_answer": "Lord of Illusions", "incorrect_answers": ["Candyman", "Needful Things", "Body Snatchers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A pearl can be produced naturally by almost any shelled mollusk. What triggers the process of pearl formation?", "correct_answer": "Irritant particles", "incorrect_answers": ["Changes in the chemical composition of the water.", "Pheromones", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Shake the following ingredients with ice: 1/2 oz. Creme De Banane, 1/2 oz. pineapple juice, 1 oz. gin, 1 oz. cream and add a dash of Grenadine.", "correct_answer": "Velvet Kiss", "incorrect_answers": ["Frozen Irish Coffee", "Silver Fizz", "White Russian"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Carol Connelly and Melvin Udall were Oscar-winning roles in this 1997 film.", "correct_answer": "As Good as it Gets", "incorrect_answers": ["Braveheart", "Chicago", "Th Last Emperor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Darth Vader has children.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What method of cooking is used in the preparation of the traditional Thai dish called Nuea pad prik?", "correct_answer": "Stir frying", "incorrect_answers": ["Boiling", "Stewing", "Baking"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Oliver Queen, who is married to Black Canary, is one of the finest archers ever. Who is his alter ego?", "correct_answer": "Green Arrow", "incorrect_answers": ["The Archer", "Green Lantern", "Archer Man"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1985 movie Weird Science, what color is the underwear Lisa is wearing when she first appears to Gary and Wyatt?", "correct_answer": "Blue", "incorrect_answers": ["Yellow", "Pink", "Red"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What future senator was the first Ph.D. on the moon?", "correct_answer": "Harrison H. Schmitt", "incorrect_answers": ["John W. Young", "David Scott", "Alan Shepard"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why is the popular Chinese Birds nest soup named so?", "correct_answer": "Because one of the ingredients is birds nest", "incorrect_answers": ["Because it is made with a large amount of thin noodles that look like a birds nest when served", "Because is is made from baby swallows", "Because it is served in a bowl arranged in a way to resemble a birds nest"]}]